<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kolors</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kolors</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kolors-3B: Unet is enough for diffusion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.&#xA;“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Multi-dimensional Human Preference for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&#xA;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/about/</guid>
      <description>Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881) 可图团队是一支专注于视觉生成和编辑算法研发的创新团队。我们致力于推动视觉生成技术的前沿发展，并将最新的研究成果应用于实际业务场景中。在可图，我们相信图像不仅仅是视觉信息的载体，更是沟通和表达的强大工具。我们致力于探索和开发能够赋予图像更多可能性的技术，让每一个用户都能轻松地创造出令人惊叹的视觉作品。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Kwai_kolors/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.&#xA;Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
